{
    "subject": "resource/Stonewall_Uprising",
    "predicate": "property/editing",
    "object": "Kate Davis",
    "human_readable": "The editing of Stonewall Uprising was done by Kate Davis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9858456254005432,
            "question": "Is Kate Davis the editor of the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9133586287498474,
            "question": "By whom was the Stonewall Uprising edited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.893834114074707,
            "question": "Who edited the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8658092617988586,
            "question": "Name the editor of the documentary Stonewall Uprising."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8636913299560547,
            "question": "Who was responsible for editing the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7908995151519775,
            "question": "What is the name of the editor for the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7108332514762878,
            "question": "What film did Kate Davis edit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49484801292419434,
            "question": "Kate Davis's editing credits include which documentary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34952062368392944,
            "question": "Kate Davis worked on what project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3145449459552765,
            "question": "What film project did Kate Davis contribute to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The editing of Stonewall Uprising was done by Kate Davis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3946_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kate Davis worked on what project?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3946_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kate Davis's editing credits include which documentary?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3946_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film did Kate Davis edit?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3946_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3946_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nThe provided text focuses on the documentary *Stonewall Uprising*,  highlighting its directors, Kate Davis and David Heilbroner, and their collaboration. There is no mention of who edited the film. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* There is no mention of an editor for the documentary \"Stonewall Uprising\".\n* However, there are multiple mentions of Kate Davis as a director and producer of the documentary, along with her husband David Heilbroner.\n* The text also states that Stonewall Uprising was directed by Kate Davis and David Heilbroner.\n\nTherefore, based on this information, I would conclude that:\n\n{ \"output\": \"no\" }"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention anything about the editing process of \"Stonewall Uprising\" or indicate that Kate Davis handled the editing. The information given focuses on the documentary's content, production details, and interviews, but does not provide any specific information regarding its editing."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several passages mention Kate Davis and David Heilbroner as the directors of the film, while there's no mention of her being involved in the editing process.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided about the editing of Stonewall Uprising being done by Kate Davis, however, there is a mention that \"Stonewall Uprising\" was directed by Kate Davis and husband David Heilbroner.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Kate Davis as the editor of Stonewall Uprising. It only mentions her as a director, along with her husband David Heilbroner.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}